[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "-- you've been a very naughty boy, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "You know what happens to naughty boys back in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Oh, this is getting weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Larry King never did this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "You know what happens to naughty boys, Ricky.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry King"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Do you feel remotely remorseful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What have I done wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "You said these terrible things about these pampered prima donnas in Hollywood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Well, what did I say that was so bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Let me remind you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "So you just conveniently came up with that line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What exactly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I mean, that was a tea party compared to your standup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What is your aim at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "I want to make people laugh, and I want to do a good job, but on my terms, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "What, you mean officials?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "With the Globes, for example.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "So, the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, they have no warning of what's coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hollywood Foreign Press Association"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Do you really think he's hurt that I didn't like \"The Tourist\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, I like your confidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Are there any limits in comedy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "There's nothing you shouldn't joke about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "You take the art of comedy pretty seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "I don't know, Ashton Kutcher, Bruce Willis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashton Kutcher", "Bruce Willis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Bruce was there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Was he joking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Of course he was joking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "How do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "ERVAIS: Because I've met him, and he's got a great sense of humor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Did you meet him afterwards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 343, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "But do you care -- let me ask you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Do you care about what they may be going through in their private lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, I don't know if they have an addiction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "If you did, would it make a difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Also, I'm not judging them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "You're mocking them, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What's up with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Well, if you're a believer in God, if you're a Christian, as many tens of millions in America are --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What, because I'm saying I don't believe in God?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes, because you're kind of mocking them there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "And what happened to change your mind then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I used to go to Sunday school all the time, I believed in -- well, you've got to realize that when you're a working class kid -- I came from a very poor, working class background.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "What do you think will happen to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I'll be rewarded now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "But when you die, what do you think happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "People who liked me will remember me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Are you a spiritual person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, not in that sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I don't believe there's anything after.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "When you see lists like that, you must laugh, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Oh, I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Anything you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "I mean, you're a good-looking lad, but it's pretty camp, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "It's much more than camp.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "And Spandau?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CC", "IN", ":", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "You're proud of yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I know and that -- and that's got about three or four socks down there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ":", "WRB", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "RP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 550, "question": "And you still can't tell, can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "But you used to be -- when \"The Office\" came out, the great thing about you was --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "-- you were just chunky, chubby Ricky --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What was the point when you went -- how -- how heavy were you when you went that's enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Fourteen stone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Right, you made it; you worked hard to get it, I can't blow this; I've got to now play this game seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Not then, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes, yes, I didn't -- I didn't ever worry about my weight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "How much have you lost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "About 25 pounds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "And how have you done it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Working out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jesus"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "ORGAN: Any nip and tuck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Oh, Jesus, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "No, nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 616, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "But I've -- I've -- I have those things on --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Have you got vainer, do you think, since you've been a TV and film star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Do you like being famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Not at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Are you -- are you easy to live with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Would Jane say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "You just don't believe in God, so what's the point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Is that a deliberate, conscious decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "ERVAIS: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "I'll bet you'd be a good dad, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "I -- I -- oh, I love kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have someone like Jane, then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Without being cheesy about it, what has been the secret to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "There's no secret.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Well, that's -- that's important, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", ":", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "And that, after 25 years or more, is a pretty amazing achievement --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cuba"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "What did she say to you after the Globes this year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "She said I've -- I've got the fast car, here's your disguise and I've got two tickets to Cuba.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "It is true, but it was meant to be a secret one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "What's the part you play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "I just bump into Steve Carell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "So you play David Brent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "Yes, you just act like an idiot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Brent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 828, "question": "When you first saw Steve Carell playing his version, did you feel like I did, ah, what a relief, he can do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 829, "answer": "Oh yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "Did Steve tell you that he was leaving the American version?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "Yeah, well, I sent him an email saying I think you did the right thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hardy"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "If you could be trapped on a desert island with three other comedians in history, who would they be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "Laurel and Hardy would count for two of them straight away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Comedian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "The funniest man you've ever seen or woman in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "If you had five minutes left to live, what's the joke you'd tell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "There's four jokes I just realized I can't tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 906, "question": "It is two season and bang?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 907, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "Which is a brilliant question, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "A great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "Are you mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 928, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd be too busy to be in three of the greatest franchises in movie history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 929, "answer": "I knew they were good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 931, "question": "But did you ever think, when you were a young Ricky Gervais, that you could ever be in that position, to turn movies down like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 932, "answer": "ERVAIS: I never thought about I'd ever be offered a movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 940, "question": "How many DVDs have you sold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 941, "answer": "Probably about seven or eight million.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 942, "question": "So how rich are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 943, "answer": "Oh, come on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "Are you richer than him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 966, "question": "What were the values that they instilled in you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 967, "answer": "Work hard and pay your way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 970, "question": "And do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 971, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 973, "question": "Do you get to enjoy the fruits of your hard work, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 974, "answer": "No, I enjoy the hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 992, "question": "What values do you think they instilled in you as a young -- a young George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 993, "answer": "My father taught me never to mix grain and grape at a very young age.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}]